[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "From what you understand of what the president will be revealing tomorrow, as what he wants to push forward with, is that enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "It is a fantastic start, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Can it actually become law?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, that remains to be seen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Is it as shocking as many would have us believe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Yes, it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Will they just go and find some other weapon that can do the same job for them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, this is like Sandy Hook certainly to motivate us to do some reasonable, sensible things that we -- that we must do about gun violence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "How do you deal with the Americans who say, no, you're not having any of my guns, it's my Second Amendment right to bear arms, I can have all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "WP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, first of all, no one is talking about taking anyone's weapon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Well, that's not good enough anymore, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, listen, I agree with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Dr. Fox, do you want to jump in here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Why is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, because evil is going to happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["First Amendment"]}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Where do we draw the line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "But the First Amendment refers to the freedom of expression, on speech and for the press.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1934"]}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Why -- why ban machine guns then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Machine guns were banned in 1934 as a result of the National Firearms Act.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2009"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Joe Biden"]}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "What does that tell you about -- as a reaction to Aurora and then Sandy Hook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Well, Piers, look, the reality is, is that gun sales sigh rocketed upon the election of Barack Obama and Vice President Joe Biden in 2009.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Aurora"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "When you hear people say there's just no comparison between, say, the M-16 military weapon and an AR- 15, what is your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, I understand what his position is and it's a little bit of semantics.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["15"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "What does any civilian need one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "To protect myself and protect my family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 345, "question": "You believe that an American government in the modern age is going to turn tyrannical?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 346, "answer": "No, I'm not saying --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "That you would need an AR-15 to protect yourself against your own government?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Well, let's look at it right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Government's monopoly on violence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "No, the government has a monopoly on legitimate violence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "To have an AR-15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "To have any gun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Why do you need an AR-15?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Because I do want to protect my family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "What else do you call it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "You and I agree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "The question is, how many would if they didn't have guns in their homes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "They would find something else.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "How do you convince them this is not an attack on their rights, if you like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "It is not an attack on their rights.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "I mean, how are you going to tell my children that nothing has been done after what happened to our family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "But, Piers, the truth of the matter is this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "When you have a family like this who has been destroyed over what has happened -- you saw, Ashley -- Kendra, when you hear people try to just insist on saying these AR-15 weapons are not assault weapon, what do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "It's really impossible for me to understand that the killers could get that kind of power in their hands.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ashley -- Kendra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "When you hear people talk in this way and just have no apparent comprehension, I think, of why you want these kind of weapons taken away, what is your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "Well, I agree with this lady about it is our Constitutional right to have -- bear arms.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130115pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Do you think he's got it about right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "I hope to see a ban on assault rifles or much stricter possession of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]